A Guide to the Robert N. Giaimo Papers 1980.0003
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series V: Outgoing Correspondence, 1959-1980
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4616)
    - North Haven, 1978 (Box 169:, Folder 6667)
    - O, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6668-6669)
    - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6670)
    - Orange, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6671)
    - P, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6672-6680)
    - Postal Service, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6681)
    - Q - R, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6682-6688)
    - Railroad Retirement Board, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6689)
    - Rules Commission, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6690)
    - S, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6691-6703)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6704)
    - Selective Service, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6705)
    - Senate, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6706)
    - Small Business Administration (SBA), 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6707)
    - Smithsonian, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6708)
    - Social Security Administration (SSA), 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6709)
    - Speaker of the House, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6710)
    - State, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6711)
    - Stratford, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6712)
    - T, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6713-6715)
    - Transportation, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6716)
    - Treasury, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6717)
    - U - V, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6718-6720)
    - Veterans Administration (VA), 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6721)
    - W, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6722-6726)
    - Wallingford, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6727)
    - Ways and Means Committee, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6728)
    - West Haven, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6759)
    - White House, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6760)
    - Woodbridge, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6761)
    - X - Z, 1978 (Box 170:, Folder 6762-6764)
    - A, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6765-6769)
    - ACTION, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6770)
    - Agriculture, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6771)
    - Air Force, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6772)
    - Alcohol, Tobacco and Firearms (ATF), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6773)
    - Amtrak, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6774)
    - Appropriations Committee, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6775)
    - Architect, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6776)
    - Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6777)
    - Army, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6778)
    - Army Corps of Engineers, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6779)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6780)
    - B, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6781-6789)
    - Botanical Gardens, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6790)
    - Branford, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6791)
    - C, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6792-6800)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6801)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6802)
    - Civil Service, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6803)
    - Clinton, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6804)
    - Coast Guard, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6805)
    - Commerce, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6806)
    - Commission on Civil Rights, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6807)
    - Community Services Administration, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6808)
    - Congressional Budget Office, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6809)
    - Congressional Committees, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6810)
    - Congressional Operations Committee, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6811)
    - Connecticut Officials, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6812)
    - Conrail, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6813)
    - Consuls, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6814)
    - Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6815)
    - Cost of Living Council, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6816)
    - D, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6817-6823)
    - District of Columbia Government, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6824)
    - Defense, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6825)
    - E, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6826)
    - East Haven, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6827)
    - Economic Development Administration, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6828)
    - Energy, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6829)
    - Energy Research and Development Administration, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6830)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6831)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6832)
    - Executive Office, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6833)
    - F, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6834-6839)
    - Federal Aviation Association (FAA), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6840)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6841)
    - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6842)
    - Federal Deposit Insurance Commission (FDIC), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6843)
    - Federal Election Commission, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6844)
    - Federal Energy Commission, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6845)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6846)
    - Federal Manpower Commission, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6847)
    - Federal Maritime Commission, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6848)
    - Federal Register, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6849)
    - Federal Railroad Administration, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6850)
    - Federal Reserve Board, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6851)
    - Federal Telecommunications Systems, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6852)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6853)
    - Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6854)
    - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6855)
    - G, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6856-6862)
    - Government Accounting Office (GAO), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6863)
    - General Services Administration (GSA), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6863)
    - Government Printing Office (GPO), 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6864)
    - Guilford, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6865)
    - Ha - Hh, 1979 (Box 171:, Folder 6866)
    - Hh - Hz, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6867-6871)
    - Hamden, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6872)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6873)
    - House Administration Committee, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6874)
    - House of Representatives, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6875)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6876)
    - I, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6877)
    - Immigration, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6878)
    - Inaugural, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6879)
    - Independent Agencies, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6880)
    - Intelligence Commission, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6881)
    - Interior, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6882)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6883)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6884)
    - J, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6885-6887)
    - Justice, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6888)
    - K, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6889-6893)
    - Killingworth, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6894)
    - L, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6895-6901)
    - Labor, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6902)
    - Library of Congress, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6903)
    - M, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6904-6912)
    - Madison, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6913)
    - Marine Corps, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6914)
    - Milford, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6915)
    - N, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6916-6918)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6919)
    - National Bureau of Standards, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6920)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6921)
    - National Guard, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6922)
    - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6923)
    - National Science Foundation, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6924)
    - Navy, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6925)
    - New Haven, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6926)
    - North Branford, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6927)
    - North Haven, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6928)
    - O, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6929-6930)
    - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6931)
    - Orange, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6932)
    - P, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6933-6941)
    - Postal Service, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6942)
    - Q - R, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6943-6949)
    - Railroad Retirement Board, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6950)
    - Rules Committee, 1979 (Box 172:, Folder 6951)
    - S, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6952-6964)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6965)
    - Selective Service, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6966)
    - Senate, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6967)
    - Small Business Administration (SBA), 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6968)
    - Smithsonian, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6969)
    - Social Security Administration (SSA), 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6970)
    - Speaker of the House, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6971)
    - State, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6972)
    - Stratford, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6973)
    - T, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6974-6776)
    - Transportation, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6777)
    - Treasury, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6778)
    - U, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6779)
    - United Nations, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6780)
    - V, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6781-6782)
    - Veterans Administration (VA), 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6783)
    - W, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6784-6788)
    - Wallingford, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6789)
    - Ways and Means Committee, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6790)
    - West Haven, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6791)
    - White House, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6792)
    - Woodbridge, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6793)
    - X - Z, 1979 (Box 173:, Folder 6794-6796)
    - A, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6797-6802)
    - ACTION, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6803)
    - Agriculture, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6804)
    - Air Force, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6805)
    - Amtrak, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6806)
    - Appropriations Committee, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6807)
    - Architect, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6808)
    - Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6809)
    - Army, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6810)
    - Army Corps of Engineers, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6811)
    - B, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6812-6820)
    - Botanical Gardens, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6821)
    - Branford, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6822)
    - C, 1980 (Box 173:, Folder 6823-6831)
    - Census Bureau, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6832)
    - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6833)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6834)
    - Clinton, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6835)
    - Coast Guard, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6836)
    - Commerce, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6837)
    - Commission on Civil Rights, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6838)
    - Community Services Administration, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6839)
    - Congressional Budget Offic, e, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6840)
    - Congressional Committees, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6841)
    - Congressional Operations Commission, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6842)
    - Connecticut Officials, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6843)
    - Conrail, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6844)
    - Consuls, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6845)
    - Consumer Product Safety Commission, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6846)
    - D, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6847-6853)
    - Defense, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6854)
    - District of Columbia Government, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6855)
    - E, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6856)
    - East Haven, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6857)
    - Economic Development Administration, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6858)
    - Education, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6859)
    - Energy, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6860)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6861)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6862)
    - Executive Office, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6863)
    - F, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6864-6868)
    - Federal Aviation Association (FAA), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6869)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6870)
    - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6871)
    - Federal Deposit Insurance Commission (FDIC), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6872)
    - Federal Election Commission, >, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6873)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6874)
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6875)
    - Federal Maritime Commission, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6876)
    - Federal Railroad Administration, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6877)
    - Federal Register, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6878)
    - Federal Reserve Board, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6879)
    - Federal Telecommunications Systems, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6880)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6881)
    - Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6882)
    - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6883)
    - G, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6884-6890)
    - Government Accounting Office (GAO), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6891)
    - General Services Administration (GSA), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6892)
    - Government Printing Office (GPO), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6893)
    - Guilford, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6894)
    - H, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6895-6901)
    - Hamden, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6902)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6903)
    - House Administration Commission, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6904)
    - House of Representatives, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6905)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6906)
    - I, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6907)
    - Immigration, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6908)
    - Inaugural, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6909)
    - Independent Agencies, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6910)
    - Interior, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6911)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6912)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6913)
    - J, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6914-6916)
    - Justice, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6917)
    - K - L, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6918-6928)
    - Labor, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6929)
    - Library of Congress, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6930)
    - M - Me, 1980 (Box 174:, Folder 6931-6936)
    - Mf - Mz, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6937-6939)
    - Madison, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6940)
    - Marine Corps, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6941)
    - Milford, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6942)
    - N, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6943-6945)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6946)
    - National Bureau of Standards, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6947)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6948)
    - National Guard, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6949)
    - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6950)
    - National Science Foundation, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6951)
    - Navy, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6952)
    - New Haven, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6953)
    - North Branford, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6954)
    - North Haven, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6955)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6956)
    - O, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6957-6958)
    - Office of Management and Budget (OMB), 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6959)
    - Office of Personnel Management, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6960)
    - Orange, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6961)
    - Q - P, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6962-6971)
    - Postal Service, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6972)
    - R, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6973-6978)
    - Railroad Retirement Board, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6979)
    - Rules Committee, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6980)
    - S, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6981-6990)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6991)
    - Selective Service, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6992)
    - Senate, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6993)
    - Small Business Administration (SBA), 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6994)
    - Smithsonian, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6995)
    - Social Security Administration (SSA), 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6996)
    - Speaker of the House, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6997)
    - State, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6998)
    - Stratford, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 6999)
    - T, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7000-7002)
    - Transportation, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7003)
    - Treasury, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7004)
    - U, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7005)
    - United Nations, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7006)
    - V - W, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7007-7012)
    - Wallingford, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7013)
    - Ways and Means Committee, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7014)
    - West Haven, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7015)
    - White House, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7016)
    - Woodbridge, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7017)
    - X - Z, 1980 (Box 175:, Folder 7018-7020)
  - P, 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4617-4620)
  - Post Office, 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4621)
  - Q - S, 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4622-4630)
  - Selective Service, 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4631)
  - Selective Service Administration (SSA), 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4632)
  - State (Department of), 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4633)
  - T, 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4634-4635)
  - Treasury (Department of), 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4636)
  - U - V, 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4637-4638)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4639)
  - W - Z, 1965 (Box 141:, Folder 4640-4644)
  - A, 1966 (Box 141:, Folder 4645-4648)
  - Air Force, 1966 (Box 141:, Folder 4649)
  - Architect, 1966 (Box 141:, Folder 4650)
  - Army, 1966 (Box 141:, Folder 4651)
  - B - Cr, 1966 (Box 141:, Folder 4652-4659)
  - Commerce, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4661)
  - Congressional Records, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4662)
  - Consuls, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4660)
  - D, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4663-4666)
  - Defense, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4667)
  - E - H, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4668-4680)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4681)
  - I, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4682)
  - Immigration, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4683)
  - J - L, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4684-4692)
  - Labor, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4693)
  - Library of Congress, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4694)
  - M, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4695-4699)
  - Marines, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4700)
  - N, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4701)
  - Navy, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4702)
  - O, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4703)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4704)
  - P, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4705)
  - Post Office, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4706)
  - Q - Rf, 1966 (Box 142:, Folder 4707-4708)
  - Rg - S, 1966 (Box 143:, Folder 4709-4715)
  - Selective Service, 1966 (Box 143:, Folder 4716)
  - Social Security Administration (SSA), 1966 (Box 143:, Folder 4717)
  - State, 1966 (Box 143:, Folder 4718)
  - T - V, 1966 (Box 143:, Folder 4719-4722)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), 1966 (Box 143:, Folder 4723)
  - W, 1966 (Box 143:, Folder 4724-4725)
  - White House, 1966 (Box 143:, Folder 4726)
  - X - Z, 1966 (Box 143:, Folder 4727-4729)
  - A, 1967 (Box 143:, Folder 4730-4733)
  - Air Force, 1967 (Box 143:, Folder 4734)
  - Architect, 1967 (Box 143:, Folder 4735)
  - Army, 1967 (Box 143:, Folder 4736)
  - B - C, 1967 (Box 143:, Folder 4737-4744)
  - Commerce, 1967 (Box 143:, Folder 4745)
  - Consuls, 1967 (Box 143:, Folder 4746)
  - D, 1967 (Box 143:, Folder 4747-4750)
  - Defense, 1967 (Box 143:, Folder 4751)
  - E - Fo, 1967 (Box 143:, Folder 4752-4755)
  - Fg - G, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4756-4760)
  - General Service Administration (GSA), 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4761)
  - H, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4762-4765)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (HEW), 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4766)
  - Housing and Urban Development (Department of) (HUD), 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4767)
  - I, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4768)
  - Immigration, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4769)
  - J - L, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4770-4777)
  - Labor, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4778)
  - Library of Congress, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4779)
  - M, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4780-4786)
  - Marines, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4787)
  - N, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4788-4789)
  - Navy, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4790)
  - New Haven Office, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4791)
  - O, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4792)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO), 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4793)
  - P, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4794-4797)
  - Post Office, 1967 (Box 144:, Folder 4798)
  - Q - Sn, 1967 (Box 145:, Folder 4799-4806)
  - Selective Service, 1967 (Box 145:, Folder 4809)
  - So - Sz, 1967 (Box 145:, Folder 4807-4808)
  - Social Security Administration (SSA), 1967 (Box 145:, Folder 4810)
  - State, 1967 (Box 145:, Folder 4811)
  - T, 1967 (Box 145:, Folder 4812-4813)
  - Treasury, 1967 (Box 145:, Folder 4814)
  - U - V, 1967 (Box 145:, Folder 4815-4816)
  - Veterans Administration (VA), 1967 (Box 145:, Folder 4817)
  - W - Z, 1967 (Box 145:, Folder 4818-4823)
  - A, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4824-4827)
  - Air Force, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4828)
  - Architect, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4829)
  - Army, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4830)
  - B - C, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4831-4838)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4839)
  - Commerce, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4840)
  - Committees, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4841)
  - Consuls, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4842)
  - D, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4843-4846)
  - Defense, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4847)
  - E - Gd, 1968 (Box 145:, Folder 4848-4853)
  - Ge - Gz, 1968 (Box 146:, Folder 4854-4856)
  - General Service Administration (GSA), 1968 (Box 146:, Folder 4857)
  - H, 1968 (Box 146:, Folder 4858-4861)
- Series VI: Press Releases and Statements, 1959-1980
  - 1959 January - 1962 October (Box 176)
  - 1962 October - 1965 December (Box 177)
    Scope and Content Note
    Press releases and their drafts; newsletters and their drafts; statements; speeches and their drafts
  - 1966 January - 1967 May (Box 178)
  - 1967 May - 1968 October (Box 179)
  - 1968 November - 1969 June (Box 180)
  - 1969 July - 1970 August (Box 181)
  - 1970 September - 1971 June (Box 182)
  - 1971 June - 1972 June (Box 183)
  - 1972 June - 1973 June (Box 184)
  - 1973 July - 1974 August (Box 185)
  - 1974 September - 1975 July (Box 186)
  - 1975 August - 1976 September (Box 187)
  - 1976 September - 1977 April (Box 188)
  - 1977 May - October (Box 189)
  - 1977 November - 1978 May (Box 190)
  - 1978 June - September (Box 191)
  - 1978 September - 1979 April (Box 192)
  - 1979 May - December (Box 193)
  - 1980 January - August (Box 194)
  - 1980 September - December (Box 195)
- Series VII: Project Files, undated, 1962-1980
  - Subseries A: Connecticut
    - CETA (Box 196)
    - CPI
    - CPI (Box 197)
    - CPI (Box 198)
    - Dixwell Legal Rights Association
    - New Haven Legal Assistance Association
    - OEO Program Information
    - New Haven Youth Development
    - Connecticut Business and Industry (Box 199)
    - General (Box 200-204)
    - Education (Box 205-207)
    - Education (Box 208)
    - Post Office
    - Rivers and Harbors (Box 209-211)
    - Rivers and Harbors (Box 212)
    - Rail and New Haven Harbor
    - Transportation
      - Railroads
      - Railroads (Box 213)
      - Mass Transit (Box 214)
      - General
      - Highways
      - Airways
      - Airways (Box 215)
    - Passports (Box 216)
    - Dickey Lincoln Project (Box 217)
  - Subseries B: Federal Grants and Contracts Awards
    - Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 218:, Folder 7021-7023)
    - Labor (Box 218:, Folder 7024)
    - Interior (Box 218:, Folder 7025)
    - Housing and Urban Development (Box 218:, Folder 7026-7027)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (Box 218:, Folder 7028-7029)
    - Other Departments and Agencies (Box 218:, Folder 7030-7032)
    - Contract Announcements (Box 218:, Folder 7033)
    - Press Releases (Box 218:, Folder 7034-7036)
    - Office of Education (Box 218:, Folder 7037-7039)
    - Department of Transportation (Box 218:, Folder 7040)
    - Armed Services (Box 218:, Folder 7041-7045)
    - Department of Labor (Box 218:, Folder 7046-7047)
    - Avco-Army (Box 218:, Folder 7048)
    - General Service Administration (Box 218:, Folder 7049)
    - Agriculture (Box 218:, Folder 7050)
    - Public Health (Box 218:, Folder 7051)
    - NASA Grants (Box 218:, Folder 7052)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (Box 218:, Folder 7053)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 218:, Folder 7054)